hdwallpapersbest.com 2014-07-31

# Privacy Policy | HD Wallpapers Best

You are here: [Home](http://www.hdwallpapersbest.com/) » Privacy Policy

At HDWallpapersBest.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit HDWallpapersBest.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Server Logs**  
As with most other websites, HDWallpapersBest.com logs web, database, and other server-software usage and access information. This information may include your internet protocol (IP) address, which in many cases can be translated to an affiliation (such as your work, school, or internet service provider), or a geographical location. We only use this information for debugging purposes and for aggregating into anonymous usage and traffic statistics.

**Cookies**  
While browsing HDWallpapersBest.com, a small number of text files referred to as cookies are created on your local file system by your web browser at the request of our servers. These files allow us to personalize the browsing experience for users. You are free to delete them at any time, or configure your browser not to create them. However, we do not guarantee that every feature of HDWallpapersBest.com will function as expected without cookies enabled.

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
HDWallpapersBest.com serves ads provided by a range of third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by HDWallpapersBest.com’s privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience we provide a list our advertising partners below. Unfortunately we cannot guarantee it is always comprehensive and up to date.

Google, We present you the following information about Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx): Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
